

Amblessed Fon Abongwa

A Web Designer's Portfolio

https://amblessedfonabongwa.github.io/Portfolio/

I am a highly skilled and adaptable web designer with a strong background in Graphics and Web Designing. With expertise frontend frame works like React Js and Next.Js as well as being a Figma expert, I excel in creating visually appealing and user-friendly websites. I possess excellent communication skills and can work well under pressure, ensuring that tasks are completed efficiently and effectively. I am dedicated to delivering high-quality results and exceeding client expectations.

Experience

Stephen's Graphics and Web.Co

Frontend Developer

Douala

November 2022-January 2024

- -Relating to Clients to Determine their Preferences.
- -Using Html5,Tailwind CSS, And JavaScript frameworks(React/Next.js) to Create Responsive Designs for Clients.
- -Figma UX, UI Prototype Building for Websites, Applications etc.
- -Communicating with clients to determine optimum results.
- -Frontend Design as well as Backend Design Projects.
- -Photoshop picture edittng and flyers making.

Freelance

Web Designer

Douala

September 2022-Present

- -Developing Advanced Websites for clients.
- -Polishing and making Logos with Adobe Illustrator.
- -Building Prototype Projects with Figma.

Education

IUGET University

Graphics And Wed Design

Information And Technology

2022-Present

Amasia Bilingual College

Information Technology

Advanced Level Industrial Studies

March 2019-June 2021

Amasia Bilingual College

Computer Science

Ordinary Level Industrial Studies

March 2017-January 2019

Projects

Design Projects

https://amblessedfonabongwa.github.io/Portfolio/

References

https://amblessedfonabongwa.github.io/Portfolio/

Portfolio Website

Skills

HTML5, Tailwind, Javascript

Figma Expert

React and Next Js

Client Relation

Efficient with Adobe Photoshop

Databases Like MongoDb & MySQL

Interests

Football

Photography, Video Shooting and Editing

Languages

English



French